Did you see the look Maggie gave me?
Maggie didn't give you a look.
She knows what happened.
She doesn't know who it happened with.
Well. it's only a matter of time.
Horses seem better. so I'm... I'm going.
- You should take Ruben with you.
- Maggie. I don't know.
You're saying you don't
wanna go with the husband
of the woman that you've been fucking?
- You must be Maggie.
- This is lt. Olsen.
A big part of my job was to locate
and isolate Carmen navarro.
He's not who he says
he is. And all of this.
whatever it's for. it's not fucking good.
- Edward!
- Anybody here?
Carmen! Brian!
My god.
Hello?
Jesus...
A conundrum. That's what this is.
Cause I don't know if you're here to
help me or finish the job. you know?
I'm gonna need you to give
me one really good reason
why I shouldn't finish this cigarette
and shoot you in the fucking head.
You've come to finish me off?
I'm gonna be the one
who fucking finishes you.
I swear to you. I just came here for help.
I told you. Another man in a mask
- mcnab.
- Yeah. He...
He was at our house. We live nearby.
Why don't you stop fucking lying?!
I am not lying! I swear
to god I'm not lying!
I am not lying! I'm
telling you. my son is sick.
He is really. really sick!
That's the bullshit part. Why come here?
- Because...
- Why not go to a fucking hospital?
Please.
Please. please. please... Please.
Fuck!
Okay.
I'm telling you. we tried
to get into town. but...
This part is gonna
sound like bullshit. I know.
but there's this paint. okay?
This blue line of paint on the ground
marking this. I don't
know what you call it.
this kind of... This kind of force field.
If you cross the line. you die!
Listen to you.
Acting like you're telling the truth.
like I don't know what lies sound like.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Keep playing dumb.
- I'm gonna put a bullet in your stomach.
- I am not lying!
Not about my son. not about the line.
and not about the goddamn force field!
Stop fucking saying "force field"!
If you'd really met mcnab.
you'd know that's not what it is.
Okay. fine. What the hell is it then?
I'm telling you. it's a trap.
A cage.
An invisible. goddamn death trap cage.
How it works is miles
above my pay grade.
And besides. the "how"
of it doesn't matter.
What matters is it's real.
it's bad. and you can't fucking see it!
Take it down a notch.
Hey. new guy. Travis.
What the hell you doin'?
Sorry. I'm... just... Jesus.
You don't even know the
trap's there until it's too late.
You think you're going for a walk.
and then. bam! Just like that...
You're dead.
I mean. they make it that way
so nobody'll know the trap's there.
Think they're so fucking clever.
But I know it's there.
- Suddenly...
- Wait... Who's "they" again?
Visitors.
That's right. That's right.
I would've called them little green men.
but you call 'em visitors.
And any one of us in here could be...
One of these visitors.
Even you. Right?
I could be.
Yes.
Word to the wise.
Don't let mcnab follow
you into the bathroom
unless you wanna get probed.
Yeah. that's funny.
But do me a favor.
Try laughing at this.
- Jesus.
- Yeah... That's what I thought.
All I did was brush up
against the edge of the trap.
- Barely touched it.
- No one needs to see that.
This is real.
This is happening!
And not someday.
It's happening now.
They are here.
And they walk among us!
That's it! You're done. I told ya.
Give me your keys.
Now. Come on.
How am I supposed to get home?
Not my problem. mcnab.
Taking my keys. big al.
makes it your problem.
What about him?
Fine. New guy? Here.
Catch.
That scar.
What about it?
What really happened?
I said what really happened.
And you've got no idea how this
invisible death trap thing works?
Doesn't mean it's not real.
Yeah. but it has to
have something. right?
Some kind of energy or power source.
There's a source.
It's like nothing you've ever seen.
It's... it's iridescent. and it's alive.
Get near it. and it calls out to you
like a... like a siren song.
Like a what?
Like a bug light.
It lures you in.
Mesmerizes you.
Closer and closer...
Until. zap!
Give me a reason why I'd lie.
Most people don't need a reason.
Let you in on a little secret?
I'm not most people.
Hey...
For fuck's sake.
You okay in there?
I'm coming in.
What the fuck?
Whoa! Whoa. I was just...
I-I was just checking on you.
Just don't.
I don't care.
Don't care if anybody...
Thinks I'm full of shit. either.
A liar.
Off my rocker.
But you.
I see it in your eyes. Travis.
You see what?
You're asking yourself
"what if this crazy. old bastard's
actually telling the truth?"
I am not some kind of alien in disguise.
Which is exactly
what an alien in disguise would say.
Just shut up and don't fucking move.
How then? Hey.
How do I prove I'm not
one of these visitors?
That's the whole thing.
You can't.
Mcnab would have told you that.
Well. he wasn't exactly talking to me.
He just pointed a gun at us and
wrote down on this whiteboard thing. so.
Listen... I-I don't know what happened
or what's happening here. but hey.
I do know you need help. You do.
My wife. she's a doctor. We
have medicine. She can help
thought you needed help for your son.
Now your wife's a fuckin' doctor?
Can't keep your goddamn story straight.
Not that kind of doctor.
She's a veterinarian.
Just fuckin' stop. Doctor. Veterinarian.
Sick kid. No idea what happened here.
Or you're not lying and you do need help.
Fucking conundrum.
All I ever wanted was a little control.
Control over my life.
over what happens to me.
Idiot I am.
I fell for it.
You're smart. on the ball.
You know what I'm talking about.
Guys on TV. the Internet.
going on about flying saucer. ufos.
alien autopsies.
All bullshit.
And all based on something you can see.
Guy in a rubber suit type stuff.
What I'm saying. is no... body.
No nothing.
No there there.
Travis! If I... Think...
non-corporeal entities.
No ufos?
Who needs a spaceship
when you don't have a body?
Yeah. but meteors?
Thousands of meteors smack
into earth every single year.
A visitor just hitches a ride.
and nobody blinks an eye.
Think about it.
And they steal our bodies?
I didn't say "steal."
I said "inhabit."
Control.
Hey. listen.
I don't need you to be a true believer.
at least not until you truly believe.
I'm just glad you're still listening.
It means you got a critical brain.
No judgment.
No scoffing. Just...
Take it in. weigh the evidence...
Then decide for yourself.
Then what do they do?
After they inhabit you?
You got good visitors. you got bad ones.
From the same place.
When a good one shows
up. a bad one hunts it down.
Well. why?
Why here?
Million-dollar question.
And you zeroed right in on it.
There's that critical brain.
Razor sharp. Travis. razor sharp.
So. how come you know all this stuff?
There. look.
Right on time.
Shit. no. that-that's not
well. it could be
something. Could be nothin'.
Give me a minute.
This guy's with me.
Can he hold a gun?
- That's a good question.
- Should we find out?
Let's take a ride.
That would've flunked
you out of the academy.
Give me this.
Thumbs clear.
Point it at your target.
Line up the index and middle finger.
It's simple. effective.
What's the deal with the
photos of you guys anyway?
Shooting a stranger. that's easy.
Shooting a friend. that's hard.
So. you're not police anymore.
Me and the force parted
ways. that's correct.
That was nice. Travis. Just know.
shooting isn't what's going to save you.
A visitor. it's made of nothing.
It's like... vapor or air.
Shooting can't kill it.
And you can kill the host.
But the visitor?
It'll just hop into somebody else.
But here's the thing.
We've got our eyes on someone.
Someone who's being
inhabited by a visitor.
Shut the fuck up.
Mary Alice ducker.
Just looks like some lady. right?
- Yeah.
- Trust me.
that's a visitor.
A bad one.
How do you know?
People I'm with. Carol and Milo.
the ones in that chat room I showed you.
been following her
going on two years now.
Just following her for no reason?
There's that critical brain of yours.
Christ!
I wondered that too.
But trust me.
they have their reasons.
No deviation from her daily routine.
until two weeks ago. that is.
Then all of a sudden.
she gets real active.
Buying a gun. zip ties.
all kinds of gearing up.
getting ready kind of activities.
Jesus. I don't know about this.
Well... we do. so.
Mary Alice's behavior.
all the meteor activity.
means another visitor is coming.
A good one.
Put this up.
We don't know when
she'll make her move.
but it's going to be soon.
Clock's ticking.
When the good visitor gets here.
Mary Alice is going to hunt it down.
When she does. we hunt her down.
and she leads us right to it.
Then what?
Then we save the fucking day.
That's what.
Are you sure?
I mean. how come
you know all this stuff?
What if you're just.
I don't know...
Chasing shadows?
Baby blue.
Bluest eyes you've ever seen.
My daughter Alyssa.
Ten years ago. long before I moved here.
Alyssa. she just... Went
for a walk in the woods.
That's it. a walk.
And came back changed.
A visitor. a good one. was inhabiting her.
I thought.
I don't know what I
thought. I tried to call 9-1-1.
but the phones were dead.
The trap had already been sprung
and Alyssa was being hunted.
Then a bad visitor knocked on our door.
"My name's Adam. and I'm here to help."
Dressed like an EMT.
looked like someone who would help.
I wanted to be relieved.
but it didn't make sense.
He saw doubt on my
face. pointed a gun at me.
I froze.
He also had a bottle of this liquid.
and he drank some of it.
forced Alyssa to drink some.
Then he dragged her out of the house.
I chased after them.
But they just...
Walked through the
trap like it was nothing.
When I reached the edge of the trap.
the pain was absolute.
I mean. it was everything.
But. somehow. I fell backwards.
Of course. I tried to get back up
and go through it. but...
This time I could tell the trap was close
'cause I could feel it.
Bet I'd feel it
if one of those traps was close right now.
That ache.
And then.
at some point. the...
The trap. it was just gone.
And... Of course. by then. so were they.
It took Alyssa.
Not far.
It turned out...
Well. I'm guessing it
had someone waiting.
Someone it could move the
visitor inhabiting Alyssa into.
So. the bad one let her go.
No.
I found Alyssa...
The next morning... Dead.
Throat cut.
in a dumpster behind
a convenience store.
This is...
This is what the visitor made her drink.
This... this is the liquid.
It's yours.
- What? No. I can't...
- yes. yes.
Yes. yes. yes.
Thank you.
Nobody gets hurt?
Not if I can help it.
What do you need me to do?
I need you to drive the car.
Hey. take a zip tie.
- What am I supposed to do with it?
- Just in case.
Can you shut the fuck up?
Steady.
Is that her?
Mother fuck!
I've seen that car before.
No. that's not her.
That's fucking Hayden.
Who's Hayden?
Hayden's the asshole you're replacing.
That's his mask you're
gonna be wearing.
Replaced? I thought we were
he's gonna fucking spook her.
Hayden was a member of
our little band of brothers.
Until he preemptively shit the
fucking bed. Told you he's a psycho.
Yeah. that's right. Get
the fuck out of here.
That was fucking cutting it too close.
We're fine. We're good.
Got a visual.
That's her.
Let's go.
Whoa. Look. look.
She brought help.
Looks like a killer.
Bet she trained him to do just that.
Jesus.
All right. let's go.
Gotcha.
Woman in the doorway. See?
That's got to be our good visitor.
She just looks sick.
Jesus Christ. Meteor hits
in the immediate vicinity
less than 48 hours ago. Fact.
Our target. locked and
loaded. comes here. Fact.
And that woman is behaving exactly
like somebody who's being inhabited.
We're just gonna march up and
accuse some lady of being a killer alien?
And do what with the
other lady? Kidnap her?
- Travis.
- I'm just... I'm just trying
you wanna just sit here and watch
bad shit happen to that family?
Or you wanna save some lives?
- Fuck it. Fuck!
- Okay.
Fuck.
Eyes wide. boys! Eyes wide!
This is fucking insane.
- On the move!
- What do I do?
Just set the pool up.
No. wait. Come on.
We're not really gonna
Travis. please!
Clear!
There!
Fuck. come on.
Come on. God dammit. Fuck.
Man down. man down!
Fuck! Fuck.
Fuck.
Fuck. fuck. fuck. fuck. fuck.
Mcnab!
Stay there!
Holy...
There's no time. Travis! I'm sorry!
Mcnab!
Wait. please!
- Don't leave me!
- She's setting the trap!
Wait. please!
No!
Fuck.
Please... Please pick up. please pick up.
Please don't leave me...
Come on. mcnab. Please.
please. please don't leave me...
So the visitor... It moved into you?
The voice in my head?
The voice that's me?
There was another voice in there.
Yelling.
Angry.
A fucking battering ram of a voice.
And then everything went weird
and dizzy. and I felt like I was drowning.
But I didn't die. I just kept drowning...
Drowning and drowning in this nothing.
I tried to fucking fight it. I
tried to swim to the surface.
And... I did.
Just for a second. I-I broke through.
and I was me.
And I was able to say something.
I said. "stop."
Please. stop.
But it didn't.
Who... who are you?
Where am I?
Mcnab!
Where the fuck did you go?!
Travis. Travis?
Travis!
Shit!
Okay... look at me... Look at me...
We're gonna get... We're
gonna get you outta here.
We're gonna... we're
gonna get you to a hospital.
What... what are you saying?
Fuck it!
I was so fucked up. it moved into Olsen.
Which I thought was a
good thing. you know?
'Cause all I wanted was
to get the fuck out of there.
Hide.
I saw her go into the fucking silo.
I saw her set the trap.
And what did I do?
Just stood there.
Maybe I could have stopped her.
Maybe I could have stopped all of this.
There's got to be some way to turn
the fucking trap off. though. right?
Only one who can stop it
is the visitor who made it.
Anyone else. it'll kill 'em.
It'll draw 'em in. like a moth to flame.
then kill 'em.
I don't wanna die.
Not here. not like this.
But at least this way.
I don't have to die alone. anymore.
Please. I am begging you.
I am begging you.
All you have to do is let me go.
My aunt Julie
she's the only family who
ever gave a shit about me.
Died when I was a kid.
She believed in all this stuff.
The martians...
Lights in the sky...
We're not alone.
Wish I could tell her she was right.
Actually...
Maybe I can.
No. no. no. no. no. no!
Ruben!
James!
James.
It won't let me leave!
It's getting closer.
Don't leave me!
Hold on!
I found an ax. I can break you out.
Move away from the wall!
I can't! Just... do it now!
We gotta get home.
I don't have a fucking home!
We don't got time for this.
I'm sorry.
It just happened.
Things don't just happen.
We gotta go.
We can't just leave it.
Ruben. everyone back
at the house is in danger.
We gotta go.
Can you ride?
Fuck you.
Arlo!
My god.
Arlo! Hey.
Arlo. My god. Are you okay?
My god.